Guide to the Boehm Foundation (New York, N.Y.) Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Annual Grants, 1988-2004
  - Subseries 3.2: Annual Grants, 1988-2002
    - Annual Grants, I-O, 1988-1991
      - National Women's Law Center, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Nation Institute, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - New Israel Fund, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - New York City Civil Rights Coalition, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Oxfam America, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Annual Grants, P-W, 1988-1991
      - People for the American Way, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Ploughshares Fund, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Southerners for Economic Justice, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - United Hospital Fund, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Vazouez V. Jones, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Western States Legal Foundation, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Women's Peace Network/Military Families Support Network, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - World Policy Journal, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Institute for Women's Policy Research, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Penn Center Sea Islands Preservation Project, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Washington Office on Latin America, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy Far From Done Campaign, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives (ALBA), 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Campus Action, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Empty the Shelters, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Freedom to Travel Campaign, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Haitian Refugee Center, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Rafael Hernandez Intermediate School, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Honor Our Neighbors Origins and Rights (HONOR), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - International PEN Women's Committee, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - League of Autonomous Bronx Organizations for Renewal (LABOR), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Madre, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Maurice and Jane Sugar Law Center for Economic and Social Justice, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Montefiore Medical Center, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Pacifica Radio, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Pacific News Service, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Parliamentarians for Global Action, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Peace Development Fund, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Penn Center Sea Islands Preservation Project, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - PrairieFire Rural Action, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Sabana Litigation and AIDS Civil Rights Project, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SisterLove, Inc., 1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Social Justice Center, circa 1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Southeast Regional Economic Justice Network, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Southern Center for Human Rights, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Southern Echo, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Southerners for Economic Justice, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Students Organizing Students (SOS), 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Tennessee Industrial Renewal Network, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - United States Student Association, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Washington Office on Latin America, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Western States Legal Foundation, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Advocates for Children of New York, Inc., 1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Africa Fund, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Astraea National Lesbian Action Foundation, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Board of Education of the City of New York, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Bread and Roses, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Campus Action, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Center for Caribbean Legal Studies, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Center for Democratic Education, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Center for Human Rights Legal Action, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Center for Immigrants Rights, Inc., 1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Center ILGA Committee, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Central American Refugee Center (CARECEN), 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Central America Working Group, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Citizen Alert, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Citizens Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Coalition for Human Dignity, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correctional Association of New York, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Council on Economic Priorities, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Council on Hemispheric Affairs, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Cuban American Committee Research and Education Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - CUNY School of Law at Queens College, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Economists Allied for Arms Reduction (ECAAR), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Foundation Center, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Andrew Goodman Foundation, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Government Accountability Project (GAP), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Haitian Refugee Center, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Health Care: We Gotta Have It!, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Highlander Research and Education Center, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Honor Our Neighbors Origins and Rights (HONOR), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Indian Law Resource Center, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Institute for Security and Cooperation in Outer Space (ISCOS), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Institute for Southern Studies, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Instituto Puertorriqueño de Derechos Civiles, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - International Helping Hands, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Interns for Peace, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Long Island Alliance for Peaceful Alternatives, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Louisiana Crisis Assistance Center, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Institute, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Montana Human Rights Network, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Paul Robeson Fund for Independent Media, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Southern Center for Human Rights, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Southern Echo, Inc., 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - STEPS to End Family Violence, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Students Organizing Students (SOS), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Tennessee Industrial Renewal Network, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Women's WORLD (World Organization for Rights, Literature, and Development), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Advocates for Children of New York, Inc., 1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Africa Fund, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Campus Action, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Benjamin N. Cardozo School of Law, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Center for Democratic Education, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Center for Human Rights Legal Action, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Center for Immigrants Rights, Inc., 1995 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Center for International Policy, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Center for New Community, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Center for Women's Global Leadership, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Central American Refugee Center (CARECEN), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Coalition for Human Dignity, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Committee Against Anti-Asian Violence, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Consortium on Prison Education (COPE), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Correctional Association of New York, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Council on Economic Priorities (CEP), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Cuba Information Project, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Cuban American Committee Research and Education Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - CUNY School of Law at Queens College, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Earth Communications Radio for Peace International, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Foundation Center, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - FREESA Development Fund for South Africa, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Fundación El Pitirre, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Fund for Constitutional Government, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Fund for Popular Education, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Future Leaders Network, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Global Exchange, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Andrew Goodman Foundation, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Grassroots International, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Grassroots Leadership, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Haitian Refugee Center, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Health Care: We Gotta Have It!, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Honor Our Neighbors Origins and Rights (HONOR), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Institute for Agriculture and Trade Policy, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Institute for Food and Development Policy, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Institute for Social and Cultural Communications, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Institute for Women's Policy Research, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - International Gay & Lesbian Human Rights Commission, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - International Helping Hands, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Interns for Peace, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Irish Immigration Center, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - JusticeWorks Community, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Lambi Fund of Haiti, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Latin American Studies Association, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Latin America Working Group (Formerly Central America Working Group), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Long Island Alliance for Peaceful Alternatives, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Madre, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Madrid 1937 Abraham Lincoln Brigade Letters From The Spanish Civil War, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Media Network, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Institute, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Montana Human Rights Network, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - National Association for Public Interest Law (NAPIL), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - National Coalition for Haitian Refugees (NCHR), 1994-1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - National Commission for Democracy in México, USA, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker and Human Rights in Central America, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - National Lawyers Guild, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Neighbor to Neighbor Education Fund, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Network in Solidarity with the People of Guatemala (NISGUA), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - New Yorkers Against the Death Penalty, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - New York State Coalition Against Sexual Assault, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Normal Nursery Research Project, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - North American Congress on Latin America, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Northwest Coalition Against Malicious Harassment, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Parliamentarians for Global Action, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Political Research Associates, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - PrairieFire Rural Action, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Progressive, Inc., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Reproductive Rights Education Project, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Paul Robeson Fund for Independent Media, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Southeast Regional Economic Justice Network, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Southern Echo, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Maurice and Jane Sugar Law Center, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Symphony Space, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Tecumseh Middle School Trip to Africa Project, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Tennessee Industrial Renewal Network, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - UE Research and Education Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Interreligious Committee for Peace in the Middle East, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Vermont International Film Festival, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - WBAI--Pacifica Radio, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - White Earth Land Recovery Project, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Women's WORLD (World Organization for Rights, Literature & Development), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - World Order Models Project, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - YouthAction, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Africa Fund, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Arise for Social Justice, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now (ACORN), 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Bennington Area Arts Council, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - California Latino Civil Rights Network, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Campus Action, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Center for Commercial Free Public Education/UNPLUG, 1996-1999 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Center for Community Arts, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Center for Democratic Education, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Center for New Community, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Center for Popular Economics, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Center for Third World Organizing, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Coalition for Human Dignity, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Community Resource Center, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Consortium on Prison Education (COPE), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Correctional Association of New York, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Council on Economic Priorities, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Cuba Information Project, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - DC Student Coalition Against Racism, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Economists Allied for Arms Reduction (ECAAR), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Foundation Center, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Fundación El Pitirre (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Fund for New Priorities in America, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Future Leaders Network, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Georgia Rural Urban Summit, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Global Exchange, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Andrew Goodman Foundation, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Grassroots International, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Gray Panthers, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Hispanic AIDS Forum, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Human Serve Campaign for Universal Registration, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Food and Development Policy, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Interhemispheric Resource Center, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - International Gay & Lesbian Human Rights Commission, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - International Helping Hands, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Kentucky Local Governance Project, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Lambi Fund of Haiti, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Latin America Working Group, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Long Island Alliance for Peaceful Alternatives, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Marrowbone La Mazorca Cooperative, Inc., 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Media Ownership Project, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Institute, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Missouri Citizen Education Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Montana Human Rights Network, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - National Association for Public Interest Law (NAPIL), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - National Coalition of Education Activists (NCEA), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - National Commission for Democracy in México, USA, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - National Jobs for All Coalition, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - National Labor Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - National Lawyers Guild, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - National Security News Service, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Natural Guard, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - National Coalition Against Malicious Harassment, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Pacific News Service, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Parliamentarians for Global Action, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Penn Center Sea Island Preservation Project, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Progressive Leadership Alliance of Nevada, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Paul Robeson Fund for Independent Media, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Rural Organizing Project, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Southeast Regional Economic Justice Network, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Southern Echo, Inc., 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Maurice and Jane Sugar Law Center for Economic and Social Justice, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Symphony Space, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - WBAI--Pacifica Radio, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - White Earth Land Recovery Project, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Women's WORLD (World Organization for Rights, Literature & Development), 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Working Group on Funding Lesbian and Gay Issues, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - YouthAction, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives (ALBA), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Abya Yala Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Africa Fund, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now (ACORN), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Bill of Rights Education Project, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Bread and Roses Cultural Project, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Campus Action, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Center for Campus Organizing, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Center for Democratic Education, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Center for Human Rights Legal Action, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Center for International Policy, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Center for New Community, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Citizen's Movement for Democracy, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Coalition for Human Dignity, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Community Resource Center (CRC), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Correctional Association of New York, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Council on Economic Priorities (CEP), 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - DC Student Coalition Against Racism, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Earth Communications Radio for Peace International, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting (FAIR), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Foundation Center, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Fundación SIDA, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Gay, Lesbian, and Straight Teachers Network (GLSTN), 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Georgia Rural Urban Summit, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Global Center, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Global Exchange, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Globalvision, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Andrew Goodman Foundation, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Harlem Restoration Project, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Highlander Research and Education Center, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Institute for Agriculture and Trade Policy, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Institute for Food and Development Policy, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Interhemispheric Resource Center, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - International Gay & Lesbian Human Rights Commission, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - International Helping Hands, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Irish Immigration Center, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Lambi Fund of Haiti, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Lamp of Hope Project, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Long Island Alliance for Peaceful Alternatives, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Media Ownership Project, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Institute, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Minuteman Media, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Missouri Citizen Education Fund, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Montana Human Rights Network, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Mother Jones, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - National Alliance for Choice in Giving, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - National Coalition Against Domestic Violence, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - National Coalition for Haitian Rights, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - National Labor Committee, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - National Network for Immigrant and Refugee Rights (NNIRR), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Nevada Empowered Women's Project, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - New York State Coalition Against Sexual Assault, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Northwest Coalition Against Malicious Harassment, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Political Research Associates (PRA), 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Progressive Leadership Alliance of Nevada, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Paul Robeson Fund for Independent Media, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Rocky Mountain Media Watch, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Shared Interest, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Southeast Regional Economic Justice Network, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Southern Echo, Inc., 1997 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Maurice and Jane Sugar Law Center for Economic and Social Justice, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Sustainable America, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Symphony Space, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - UE Research and Education Fund, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - United for a Fair Economy, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - United States Urban-Rural Mission, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - U.S./Guatemala Labor Education Project, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Vermont International Film Foundation, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Washington Office on Haiti, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - WBAI--Pacifica Radio, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - White Earth Land Recovery Project, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Women's Funding Network, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - World Federalist Association, 1996-1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - YouthAction, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives (ALBA), 1998 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Africa Fund, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Appalachian Community Fund, Inc., 1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Arise for Social Justice, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Bill of Rights Education Project, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Black Radical Congress, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Black Workers for Justice, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - California Latino Civil Rights Network, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Center for Campus Organizing, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Center for International Policy, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Coalition for Human Dignity, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Community Resource Center, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Correctional Association of New York, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Critical Resistance: Beyond the Prison Industrial Complex Conference, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 21)